Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Writings and Speeches, 1912-2000 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Open Files, 1912-1993 and undated
  - Clements, George, (1-20 of 35 folders)
    - 1987. Speech. East Moves West vs. West Moves East (Box 6)
    - 1988. Speech. Is There Somebody Out There Listening to Me? (Box 6)
    - 1988. Speech. Response from the Marketplace (Box 6)
    - 1990. Speech. Creative Research (Box 6)
    - 1990. Speech. Game of Life (Box 6)
    - 1990. Speech. Market Research Agencies (Box 6)
    - 1990. Speech. Media Consumption (Box 6)
    - 1990. Speech. Perspectives on Marketing in the Future (Box 6)
    - 1990. Speech. Planning Cycle (Box 6)
  - Clements, George (continued), (21-35 of 35 folders) (Box 7)
    - 1991. Speech. Advertisng Strategies for Product Positioning (Box 7)
    - 1991. Speech. Consumer Research Guidelines (Box 7)
    - 1991. Speech. Coping with the Recession (Box 7)
    - 1991. Speech. Market Research Agencies (Box 7)
    - 1992. Speech. Game of Life (Box 7)
    - 1992. Speech. How Advertising Works (Box 7)
    - 1992. Speech. Lifestages (Box 7)
    - 1992. Speech. Marketing to 50+ (Box 7)
    - 1992. Speech. Taking Charge of Our Destiny (Box 7)
    - 1992-1993. Speech. Understanding Quebec (Box 7)
    - 1993. Speech. Is Most Advertising a Waste of Money? (Box 7)
    - 1993. Speech. Leadership through Innovation (Box 7)
    - Undated. Speech. Media speech (Box 7)
    - Undated. Speech. Research Guidelines in Advertising Development (Box 7)
  - Clurman, Ann
    - 1993. Speech. Reinventing Strategies (Box 7)
  - Cohen, Arthur
    - 1978. Article. Brand Marketing in the New Retail Environment (Box 7)
  - Colebrook, Miles
    - 1990. Speech. European Trends (Box 7)
  - Coleman, Loyd Ring
    - 1929. Article. World Grows Old (from Advertising and Selling) (Box 7)
    - 1948. Speech. What Socialism has Cost Europe and the World (Box 7)
    - 1949. Speech. Towards a Wider Thanksgiving (Box 7)
    - 1953. Speech. Guilty Men of Price Control (Box 7)
    - 1953. Speech. Religion and the Democratic Tradition (Box 7)
    - 1956. Speech. Ebbing Tide of American Foreign Investments (Box 7)
    - 1958. Article. Subliminal Advertising is 'Scientific Absurdity' Like Table Rapping, Ouija Boards: Irate Adman (Box 7)
    - 1958. Speech. Untitled (speech on Russian science to Sydney Rotary Club) (Box 7)
  - Colwell, Robert T.
    - 1957. Speech. Hard Sell or Brand Image--Do You Have to Choose? (Box 7)
    - 1958. Other writing. Creative Man's Look at the JWT Consumer Panel Personality Profile Studies (Box 7)
    - Circa 1960. Speech. Five Uses of Advertising (Box 7)
    - 1961. Speech. Inside the Interchange (Box 7)
    - 1962. Speech. Responsibilities of Advertising Agency Management (Box 7)
    - 1963. Article. Bob Colwell Reviews Jim Young (Box 7)
    - 1964. Speech. Opening Remarks on the Creative Challenge of Consumer Judgment (Box 7)
    - 1964. Speech. Writer's Footnotes to the AAAA Research (Box 7)
    - 1965. Speech. America's Attitudes toward Advertising (Box 7)
    - 1967. Speech. Some Things We Have Learned about Writing Advertising (Box 7)
  - Conlin, Ronald P.
    - 1993. Speech. Goodyear Advertising Research: Past, Present, and Future (Box 7)
  - Connell, Hugh
    - 1978-1986. Other writing. Memos and other writings (Box 7)
  - Cooney, Linda
    - 1986. Other writing. Memos and other writings (Box 7)
  - Cooper, W. Stanfield
    - 1963. Speech. What to Do When You're Faced with a Stark Naked Sheet of Paper (Box 7)
  - Corbin, Bev
    - 1975. Speech. Care and Feeding of Creative Folk (Box 7)
  - Corlett, Tom
    - 1977. Article. People's Use of Media (Box 7)
  - Courtney, Alice E.
    - 1978. Article. Canadian Perspectives on Sex Stereotyping in Advertising (with Thomas W. Whipple) (Box 7)
  - Cracraft, George A. (Box 8)
    - 1966. Article. One Small Point (Box 8)
  - Cronin, Jack, (6 folders)
    - 1974. Speech. What is a Good Magazine Ad? (Box 8)
    - 1974. Speech. Crisis at Credibility Gap (Box 8)
    - 1976. Speech. Address to British Columbia Association of Broadcasters (Box 8)
    - 1977. Speech. Smarter Spending of the Shrinking Advertising Dollar: An Agency Viewpoint of Media Trends (Box 8)
    - 1978. Speech. Advertising: It's the Response that Counts (Box 8)
    - 1978. Speech. Brilliant Package Goods Creative…Only Available Outside Canada? Pity. (Box 8)
    - 1978. Speech. Challenges We Face Together in the Next 5 Years (Box 8)
    - 1978. Speech. JWT Canada presentation to Board of Directors (Box 8)
    - 1979. Speech. Future of the Brand Label (Box 8)
    - 1980. Speech. JWT Canada Stewardship Report (Box 8)
    - 1980. Speech. Role of Advertising (Box 8)
    - 1980. Speech. Speech to JWT Worldwide Management Meeting (Box 8)
    - 1981. Speech. What It's Like to Sleep with an Elephant (Box 8)
    - 1983. Speech. Creative Tour through Europe (Box 8)
    - 1983. Speech. Manchester Publicity Association Luncheon Speech (Box 8)
    - 1983. Speech. Transnational Advertising (Box 8)
    - 1985. Speech. Advertising in Europe (Box 8)
    - 1985. Speech. Future Trends in Advertising (Box 8)
    - 1986. Speech. Creative Medium, or Creative Message? (Box 8)
    - 1986. Speech. James Webb Young/Delavan Seminar (Box 8)
    - 1987. Speech. Advertising: Visual Revolution or Creative Clutter? (Box 8)
    - 1987. Speech. JWT Principles--What We Believe (Box 8)
  - D'Aloise, Lawrence T.
    - 1968. Speech. Crux of Creativity (Box 8)
  - Daly, Derry F.
    - 1968. Other writing. Direct Mail Advertising (Box 8)
  - Danger, Lynn
    - 1981. Speech. Careers in Writing Seminar (Box 8)
  - Daniels, Barnet M.
    - 1965. Speech. How I Would Get Plus Advertising Lineage If I Were in Your Boots (speech and published version) (Box 8)
    - 1965. Article. There's Plus Lineage on the Bandwagon (Box 8)
  - Dawkins, Colin
    - 1984. Other writing. Ain't It Hell on a Windy Day (Box 8)
  - Dawn, Hazel
    - 1964. Speech. Ladies' Luncheon Speech (Box 8)
  - Day, William L., (3 folders) (Box 9)
    - 1929. Article. How Shall We Select an Advertising Agency (newsletter) (Box 9)
    - 1929. Article. What Shall the Public Think? (Box 9)
    - 1929. Other writing. What the Well Dressed Man Will Wear (humor) (Box 9)
    - 1931. Speech. Lecture to Standard Brands Incorporated Sales Class (Box 9)
    - 1932. Speech. Agency Deals with the Necessity for Creative Copy and Merchandising (Box 9)
    - 1932. Speech. General Talk on Advertising (Box 9)
    - 1932. Speech. Selling Efforts (speech to Bakery Sales Promotion Association) (Box 9)
    - Circa 1935. Article. Strategy and Tactics in Modern Advertising (Box 9)
    - 1936. Speech. Sell It AS You Must (speech and 2 published versions) (Box 9)
    - 1937. Speech. Apology for Today in Advertising (Box 9)
    - 1937. Article. How the Public Thinks (Box 9)
    - 1941. Speech. Let's Learn How to Live (Box 9)
    - Undated. Article. Fundamentals and Decadence (Box 9)
    - Undated. Article. Importance of Competitive Copy (Box 9)
    - Undated. Article. Importance of Strategy in Copy (Box 9)
    - Undated. Article. Is Advertising Crippling Manufactoring Resourcefulness? (Box 9)
    - Undated. Article. On Saving the Advertising Business (Box 9)
    - Undated. Article. One Method of Using Publicity (Box 9)
    - Undated. Article. Sales and Advertising Problems of Merged Industries (Box 9)
    - Undated. Other writing. Time and its Relation to Advertising Copy (outline) (Box 9)
    - Undated. Article. Untitled (on the principles and practice of advertising) (Box 9)
    - Undated. Other writing. Untitled (booklet on JWT and advertising) (Box 9)
    - Undated. Article. Upon Magellan's Grave Rise His Storied Riches of the Far East (Box 9)
    - Undated. Article. What about Radio? (Box 9)
  - Deaton, Don
    - 1985. Other writing. Financial summaries (Box 9)
  - De Elexpuru, Manuel
    - 1983. Other writing. Interview (Box 9)
  - Dell, Glen
    - 1985. Speech. Staff presentation, multiple versions (Box 9)
  - De Paolo, Tom
    - Circa 1970. Other writing. Celebrating Celebrity (reminiscence) (Box 9)
  - De Peterson, Peter
    - 1964. Speech. Farewell Address (Box 9)
  - Devine, C.R.
    - 1980. Speech. Citation of Don Johnston for IAA annual award (Box 9)
  - Devine, John F.
    - 1967. Article. As the Twig is Bent (Box 9)
    - 1968. Other writing. Hearings before the U.S. Equal Employment Opportunity Commission on Discrimination in White Collar Employment (transcript) (Box 9)
    - 1972. Speech. Role of Corporate Administration (Box 9)
  - De Windt, E.M.
    - 1981. Speech. Henry, Harvey, and Tom: Where Are You Now that We Really Need You? (Box 9)
  - Dhalla, Nariman, (13 folders)
    - 1973. Other writing. Basis for Formulation of Marketing Plan for JWT Domestic (Box 9)
    - 1974. Other writing. What Will the Advertising Business Be Like in Five or Six Years (Box 9)
    - Circa 1975. Article. Setting the Advertising Budget Scientifically (Box 9)
    - 1975. Article. Use of Econometric Methods for Setting Advertising Budgets (Box 9)
    - 1976. Other writing. Forecasts of National Advertising Expenditures in the United States (Box 9)
    - 1976. Article. Forget the Product Life Cycle Concept (from Harvard Business Review) (Box 9)
    - 1977. Article. How to Set Advertising Budgets (Box 9)
    - 1977. Speech. NABE address (Box 9)
    - 1978. Article. Accessing the Long-Term Value of Advertising (Box 9)
    - 1978. Other writing. Old Age Market with Special Reference to Restaurant Business (Box 9)
    - 1978. Article. Role of the Business Economist in Marketing (Box 9)
    - 1979. Article. Short-Term Forecasts of Advertising Expenditures (Box 9)
    - 1980. Article. Advertising as an Advertising Tool (Box 9)
  - Dignam, John F.
    - Circa 1980. Other writing. How to Photograph a Ford Car (handbook) (Box 9)
  - Di Paola, Vincent
    - 1980. Article. Agency Benefits from Copier Management (Box 9)
  - Dolan, Kevin
    - 1992. Speech. Snapshot of JWT International (Box 9)
  - Doyer, Bob, (2 folders)
    - 1973. Speech. His Maiden-Address as Chairman of the Board of the Dutch Association of Advertising Agencies (Box 9)
  - Durkee, Burton R.
    - Circa 1967. Article. Package Can Make Adman's Job Easy (Box 9)
  - Eagen, Dermid (Box 10)
    - 1987. Speech. Fundamentals of Communication (Box 10)
  - Eames, Herb
    - 1982. Other writing. Technology (outline of report and personal notes) (Box 10)
    - 1983. Speech. Quarter Financial Report (2nd draft) (Box 10)
  - Ebbecke, Frank
    - 1985. Speech. Hat Die Agentur Die Kreativität Gepachtet (Box 10)
  - Edens, Bob
    - 1970. Speech. Speech to Chicago Advertising Club (Box 10)
  - Effer, Gordon
    - 1963. Other writing. Interview (Box 10)
  - Ehrenberg, A.S.C.
    - 1977. Other writing. Understanding Consumer Behavior No. 1: Why Buyer Behavior? (Box 10)
  - Elton, Wallace W.
    - 1950. Speech. Comments on Creative Problems (Box 10)
    - 1956. Speech. Eyes Have It (Box 10)
    - 1957. Speech. Inner Picture (Box 10)
    - 1957. Speech. Training the Mind's Eye (speech, 2 versions) (Box 10)
    - 1962. Speech. Lady, We Need You (Box 10)
    - 1963. Article. Elton Traces Factors that Made Ford Posters Click (Box 10)
    - 1963. Speech. Need for Public Advertising (Box 10)
  - Elwood, Peter
    - 1993. Speech. Brand Equity…Severely Wounded but not Dead (Box 10)
  - Emerling, Ernie
    - 1980. Speech. What is a Brand? (with Granger Tripp) (Box 10)
    - 1993. Speech. Management of Worldwide Brands (Box 10)
  - Engle, Rafe
    - 1977. Speech. Address to ACA on advertising and the law (Box 10)
  - Erhard, Ludwig
    - 1968. Speech. Die Beziehung von Politik und Wirtschaft zue Gestaltung und Fortentwicklung des Gesundheitswesens (Box 10)
    - 1971. Speech. Die Notwendigkeit und die Rechtfertigung der Selbstmedikation aus sozialer und wirtschaftlicher Sicht (Box 10)
  - Erskine, William H.
    - 1961. Speech. Luncheon Address to Newspaper Advertising Managers Association of Eastern Canada (Box 10)
    - 1965. Speech. Retail Revolution (Box 10)
    - 1965. Other writing. Working Philosophy (statement; see also Peter Gilow Papers) (Box 10)
  - Eyman, Richard H.
    - 1973. Speech. Road to Consumer Satisfaction from the Consumer's Point of View (Box 10)
  - Farlow, Arthur C., (2 folders)
    - 1939. Article. Where are We Going with Food Industry Advertising (Box 10)
    - 1945. Article. From Advertising to War and Back (Box 10)
    - 1947. Article. Creative Advertising in Scientific Marketing (Box 10)
  - Fenning, Andy
    - Undated. Speech. Positioning (Box 10)
  - Ferchat, Robert A.
    - 1988. Speech. Speech given at Northern Telecom Canada National Sales Conference (Box 10)
  - Fergus, Lucene
    - 1962. Speech. What about the Young People (Box 10)
    - 1972. Speech. Finding and Training Better Personnel (Box 10)
  - Fickinger, Wayne
    - 1974. Speech. impact of Change...Planning for a Future Without Shock (Box 10)
    - 1976. Article. Adman Takes the Spotlight...Finally (Box 10)
    - 1976. Article. Advertising Today: From Detente to Open Warfare (2 versions) (Box 10)
    - 1976. Article. Few More of My Unfavorite Things (Box 10)
    - 1976. Speech. Overdog Snaps: Underdogs' Innovative Bite is Overrated (Box 10)
    - 1978International assignment on Advertising (interview) (Box 10)
    - 1979. Article. Action, Based on Vision, Key to 1980s (Box 10)
    - 1979. Article. Challenge is to Anticipate Course of New Electronic Media (Box 10)
    - 1979. Article. It's Time to Speculate on the Future as Year of the New Media Nears (Box 10)
    - 1980. Speech. Funny Business (Box 10)
    - Undated. Article. New Ball Game for Marketing (Box 10)
  - Field, Jane
    - Circa 1967. Other writing. Only Way to Nirvana (annotated list of recommended books) (Box 10)
  - Fielden, Edward J.
    - 1961. Speech. Address to Indian Society of Advertisers (Box 10)
  - Fields, Dave
    - Circa 1969. Speech. Untitled (Box 10)
  - Findlow, Nancy (Nan)
    - 1960. Other writing. Memorandum on speech prepared for May 10 meeting of the AMA (memorandum) (Box 10)
    - 1960. Speech. Women Will Tell You Almost Anything You Want to Know about Your Product...But There's a Catch to It (Box 10)
  - Fine, Brian
    - 1979. Speech. Use of Advertising Agencies as Marketing Research Problem Solvers (Box 10)
  - Fischer, Barbara
    - 1982. Article. Automation in Advertising (Box 10)
  - Fisher, Debra
    - Undated. Article. If the Crown Fits, Wear It (media innovation) (Box 10)
  - Fisher, Herbert
    - 1957. Speech. Panel discussion for package research conference (Box 10)
  - Florida, John
    - 1985. Speech. Address to Hill & Knowlton (Box 10)
  - Foch. Marshall
    - Circa 1976. Speech. Canada: Significant Political/Economic/Industry Trends (Box 10)
  - Foot, David
    - 1992. Speech. Predictions and Trends (Box 10)
  - Foote, Donald: See entry under Cather Lemon (Box 10)
  - Fortinberry, Glen
    - 1974. Speech. What a Client Should Expect from an Agency (Box 10)
  - Fortini-Campbell, Lisa
    - 1993. Speech. Building Brand Equity (Box 10)
  - Foster, Ann Tolstoi
    - 1971. Article. Ad Lib Takes Clue from Women (Box 10)
  - Foster, Ron
    - 1988. Speech. Review--Pat on the Back (Box 10)
    - 1989. Speech. Change and Market Expansion (Box 10)
    - 1989. Speech. Tomorrow 10 Hours Shorter (Box 10)
    - 1990. Speech. Report…An Update (Box 10)
  - Fothergill, Jack
    - 1968. Other writing. Continuing System for Planning and Evaluating Advertising Campaigns (report, with Timothy Joyce) (Box 10)
  - Francisco, Don, (2 folders)
    - 1932. Article. Informative Advertising Needed Now, More than Ever (Box 10)
    - 1937. Speech. Address before General Agents of Pacific Mutual Life Insurance Co. (Box 10)
    - 1937. Article. Address to the San Francisco Advertising Club (Box 10)
    - 1938. Speech. Force Nobody Knows--American Industry (Box 10)
    - 1938. Speech. Making America Click (Box 10)
    - 1939. Speech. Advertising--An Essential Ingredient of Democracy (Box 10)
    - 1943. Article. Short Wave Miracle Pulls the Americas Together (Box 10)
    - 1946. Speech. Does Distribution Cost Too Much (speech, and 3 printed versions) (Box 10)
    - 1948. Speech. Distribution--Look Back, and a Look Ahead (Box 10)
    - 1948. Speech. Story of Sunkist Advertising (Box 10)
    - 1950. Speech. Address given to the Association of Advertising Men (Box 10)
    - Undated. Other writing. Advertising and Merchandising Plan for the Great Gap lace Drawers Company, Inc. (pamphlet) (Box 10)
    - Undated. Other writing. Cooperative Advertising (pamphlet) (Box 10)
    - Undated. Speech. If You've Stopped Running for Trains and Winters Seem Colder, You are Getting Along Quite Normally (Box 10)
    - Undated. Speech. So You Would Like to Join an Advertising Agency (Box 10)
    - Undated. Speech. Some Advertising Gold Bricks (Box 10)
    - Undated. Speech. What's Absent from Dairy Foods (Box 10)
  - Frappier, Michel
    - 1979. Speech. International Advertising Coordination (Box 10)
  - Gannon, Frank (Box 11)
    - 1970. Other writing. Talking to Ourselves (internal report on communications in JWT) (Box 11)
  - Gardner, Edward H.
    - 1927. Other writing. Economics of Advertising (pamphlet) (Box 11)
  - Garvin, Charles E.
    - 1958. Article. Direct Mail's Big Challenge: To Meet Changing Market Requirements (Box 11)
  - Gerhold, Paul E.
    - 1965. Article. Four Roadblocks to Improved Media Measurements (Box 11)
    - 1968. Article. How to Buy Media Plus Merchandising (Box 11)
  - Ghosal, Subhas
    - 1984. Speech. Voice Over (farewell address by the C.E.O. of H.T.A.) (Box 11)
  - Gilow, Peter, (3 folders)
    - 1967. Speech. German-Speaking Markets (Box 11)
    - 1967. Speech. J. Walter Thompson Frankfurt (Box 11)
    - 1967. Speech. Wie Kann Werbung dem Export Helfen? (Box 11)
    - 1968. Speech. Kurzreferat--Evangelische Akademie, Bad Boll, Entwicklungshilfe (Box 11)
    - 1968. Speech. Referat vor dem BDW-Arbeitskreis (Box 11)
    - 1968. Speech. Werbung bereitet die Zukunft vor (Box 11)
    - 1969. Article. Ist Die Deutsche Werbung Wettbewerbsfähig? (Box 11)
    - 1969. Speech. Untitled (in German) (Box 11)
    - 1974. Speech. Government Control--A New Kind of Sales Tool (Box 11)
    - 1974. Speech. Welche Themen sollte die Aktion Gemeinsinn bei der derzeitigen wirtschlaftlichen und politischen Unsicherheit behandeln (Box 11)
    - 1975. Speech. Relation Between Agency and Industry (Box 11)
    - 1977. Speech. Growth and Diversification (Box 11)
    - 1977. Speech. Untitled (in German) (Box 11)
    - 1977. Speech. Welche Factoren Können in der Preisdifferenz zwischen Hersteller--und Endverbraucherpreis von Markenartikeln Enthalten Sein? (Box 11)
    - 1979. Speech. Challenge of the Uninvited Partner--Government Involvement in Marketing and Advertising (Box 11)
  - Gilson, Edith
    - 1980. Article. Changing Role of the Consumer in the 1980s (with Jacqueline Spielman) (Box 11)
    - 1981. Speech. Changing Role of the Consumer in the 1980s (Box 11)
    - 1981. Article. It's Not What You Say, It's What They Hear (Box 11)
    - 1982. Article. Consumer Gray Market (Box 11)
    - 1982. Article. We're All Getting Older (Box 11)
    - 1984. Other writing. Research, Reason and Risk (report) (Box 11)
    - 1985. Article. :15 Commercial Considered (Box 11)
    - 1986. Other writing. Advertising in 1990? (memo) (Box 11)
  - Glah, Roy
    - 1982. Other writing. Memorandum on Management Reference Center (Box 11)
  - Godfrey, Henry F.
    - 1949. Article. Today's Advertising Costs and What They Mean to Clients (Box 11)
    - 1952. Other writing. How Agency Research Contributes to a Creative Marketing Job (script of playlet) (Box 11)
  - Gray, John
    - 1984. Article. Viewpoints (on zapping commercials) (Box 11)
  - Grayson, David
    - 1984. Speech. JWT Asia/Pacific--Does It Really Exist? (Box 11)
  - Green, Jack R.
    - 1957. Speech. Need for Better Comparisons of Apples with Oranges (Box 11)
    - 1957. Speech. Agency Problems in Radio Usage (Box 11)
    - 1962. Other writing. Reaching the Right People in the Right Homes (comments presented in a panel discussion) (Box 11)
  - Greer, T. L.
    - 1943. Speech. Talk before the Minnesota United Nations Committee (Box 11)
  - Grisman, Arnold E., (2 folders)
    - 1981 and Undated. Speech. Roots of Human Communication (Box 11)
  - Groom, W. S.
    - 1922. Speech. Each Prospect Represents Expense and Opportunity (address) (Box 11)
  - Gross, Michael
    - 1985. Article. Creative Media Planning (Box 11)
  - Grossman, Aaron
    - 1980. Article. On a Scale of 1 to 10, What's a :10? (Box 11)
  - Gunn, Alexander
    - 1958. Speech. Going Steady--The Package and the Advertising Agency (Box 11)
    - 1963. Speech. J. Walter Thompson Company Training Programs (Box 11)
  - Gushee, Edward T., (1-21 of 57 folders)
    - Circa 1970s. Speech. Aveco speech (Box 11)
    - 1970. Speech. Ford Dealer Association (Box 11)
    - 1978. Speech. Emergence of Retailing in the Automotive Aftermarket (Box 11)
    - 1978. Speech. Marketing of Shock Absorbers (Box 11)
    - 1978. Speech. Walker meeting (Box 11)
    - Circa 1980s. Speech. High school address (Box 11)
    - Circa 1980s. Speech. Size of an Agency (Box 11)
    - 1981. Speech. Ben Bidwell going away address (Box 11)
    - 1981. Speech. (Monroe) Small Car America (Box 11)
    - 1981. Speech. Principles of Marketing (Box 11)
    - 1982. Speech. Aftermarket (Box 11)
    - 1983. Speech. (Carhartt) The Last Thing a Company Should Do. (Box 11)
    - 1985. Speech. (Carhartt) The Competition Is Us (Box 11)
    - 1986. Speech. I Didn't Know That (Box 11)
    - 1986. Speech. (J.I. Case) How High Is Up? (Box 11)
    - 1986. Speech. (J.I. Case) Ins and Outs (Box 11)
    - 1986. Speech. What Kind of Year Was It? (Box 11)
    - 1987. Speech. (J.I. Case) Change (Box 11)
    - 1987. Speech. (J.I. Case) Graduation Speech (Box 11)
    - 1987. Speech. (J.I. Case ) How High is Up? (Box 11)
    - 1987. Speech. (J.I. Case) Yellow Brick Road (Box 11)
  - Gushee, Edward T. (continued), (22-57 of 57 folders) (Box 12)
    - 1987. Speech. We Can Only Blame Ourselves (Box 12)
    - 1987. Speech. What Business Are You In? (Box 12)
    - 1988. Speech. (Carhartt) Tomorrow Happy Customers (Box 12)
    - 1988. Speech. Change (Box 12)
    - 1988. Speech. Company's Focus: Quality Planning (Box 12)
    - 1988. Speech. Customer Satisfaction (Box 12)
    - 1988. Speech. (J.I. Case) Bad Case of Indigestion (Box 12)
    - 1988. Speech. (J.I. Case) Cowboy (Box 12)
    - 1989. Speech. (Carhartt) Managing Growth (Box 12)
    - 1989. Speech. Customer is King (Box 12)
    - 1989. Speech. (J.I. Case) Grimm Look at J.I. Case (Box 12)
    - 1989. Speech. (J.I. Case) Sky is Falling (Box 12)
    - 1989. Speech. (J.I. Case) Who Are You? (Box 12)
    - 1989. Speech. Potato Council (Box 12)
    - 1990. Speech. (J.I. Case) Sines of the Times (Box 12)
    - 1990. Speech. (J.I. Case) Who Am I? (Box 12)
    - 1990. Speech. (Mike Wolf) Cue to Success (Box 12)
    - 1991. Speech. (J.I. Case) Changing Focus (Box 12)
    - 1991. Speech. (Monroe) Giant Step Backward (Box 12)
    - 1993. Speech. To JWT Worldwide Board of Directors (Box 12)
    - Undated. Speech. Account Servicing (Box 12)
    - Undated. Speech. Challenge and Failure (Box 12)
    - Undated. Speech. Death by Marketing (Box 12)
    - Undated. Speech. Exactly the Same in a Very Different Way (Box 12)
    - Undated. Speech. Gourmet speech (Box 12)
    - Undated. Speech. It's a Small World (Box 12)
    - Undated. Other writing. Jag Sheth Seminar (notes) (Box 12)
    - Undated. Speech. (J.I. Case) Company Life Cycles (Box 12)
    - Undated. Speech. (J.I. Case) We've Heard That Before (Box 12)
    - Undated. Speech. Marketing: Parity, Price, Objectivity, Advertising (Box 12)
    - Undated. Speech. (Monroe) What Business Are You In? (Box 12)